[{"answer": "It cannot not be funny! Now come on, let's stay with it, we gotta finish this today", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yeah, maybe I'll give it to my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Hey, you know, we haven't brought the my friend character into the show yet. We should try and get her into this scene", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I don't know, what do women say", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Right, right. Okay.  my friend enters.  What does she say...", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I don't know", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I don't know, what do women say", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I don't even know what they think. That's why I'm in therapy", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You know, if we bring my friend in, it's going to be so many people to keep track of. It's gonna be too hard, I'll forget where everybody's standing, you, me, my friend, the butler, it's too much", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Alright.", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yeah, yeah, so she sees me and she goes, ", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You know what I did? I snubbed her", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yeah, I know about the three dates", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "What do you mean, you snubbed her", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What do you mean, you snubbed her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Right by her", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I walked right by her", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Right by her", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "I thought there was going to be a character named my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You couldn't", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Would you care to join us", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "See ya", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I can't believe this! What was wrong with it? What didn't you like about it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "It wasn't funny? What, are you kidding", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "It wasn't funny? What, are you kidding", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "You didn't find it funny?! This is what I'm paying for", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "So, you send me to this therapist to help me with my emotional disorders, and she criticizes our script.  What kind of a therapist is that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Oh, she didn't think it was funny. What is she, my friend? We're supposed to meet with that place tomorrow! She completely shattered my confidence. And I'm paying for this, she's my employee", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "You what", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You kissed her", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I don't understand, why is this woman talking about my shoes? Why are my shoes a topic of conversation", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "\"How I'm buying my shoes now at that place's", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "What are you talking about", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I can't listen to anymore of this, the guy's losing a lung in there.", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Hi", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "It's cleavage. I couldn't look away. What am I, waiting to win an Oscar here? This is all I have in my life", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "All right. So, he caught me in a cleavage peek, so big deal. Who wouldn't look at his daughter's cleavage? She's got nice cleavage", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "All right. So, he caught me in a cleavage peek, so big deal. Who wouldn't look at his daughter's cleavage? She's got nice cleavage", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "That's why I peeked.", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "No, I... ...don't have a ketchup secret.", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Do you have a...ketchup secret", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "Because if you do have a ketchup secret, I would really, really like to know what it is.", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, it's a funny idea", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "C'mon, funny is funny", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "It's funny", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Shoes.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "Funny is funny, we're here to entertain, right", "qsentId": 48}]